<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CTF on fernetInjection</title><link>https://fernetinjection.github.io/categories/ctf/</link><description>Recent content in CTF on fernetInjection</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fernetinjection.github.io/categories/ctf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Encrypt0r</title><link>https://fernetinjection.github.io/posts/2021-02-02-encryptor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fernetinjection.github.io/posts/2021-02-02-encryptor/</guid><description>Recon This challenge had no hint and no downloadable part, it was just an ip address and a port. So let&amp;rsquo;s fire up a netcat instance and see what we&amp;rsquo;ve got:
$ nc 161.97.176.150 4449 Heres the flag! 848630917051893087050233654298398605870572417880786546004017 Enter a value for me to encrypt &amp;gt; Ok, we&amp;rsquo;ve got the flag and it looks like it&amp;rsquo;s encrypted, so we&amp;rsquo;re gonna have to get a sense for what&amp;rsquo;s going on behind the scenes just by looking at plaintext/ciphertext pairs.</description></item><item><title>cliBrowser</title><link>https://fernetinjection.github.io/posts/2021-02-01-cli-browser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fernetinjection.github.io/posts/2021-02-01-cli-browser/</guid><description>First impressions and reversing This challenge consisted of a hint:
Man I am so tired of that cringe web stack, it&amp;rsquo;s such a joke. So I made my web app in the cli, because what&amp;rsquo;s better than fancy terminal
And a binary named client that upon execution printed a banner (very cool btw) and displayed a prompt.
I started by entering some random input and got back invalid input provided, so the logical step was to search for this string.</description></item><item><title>Echo</title><link>https://fernetinjection.github.io/posts/2021-02-01-echo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fernetinjection.github.io/posts/2021-02-01-echo/</guid><description>Recon Let&amp;rsquo;s see what checksec has to say about this challenge:
$ checksec --file=./echo RELRO STACK CANARY NX PIE RPATH RUNPATH Symbols FORTIFY Fortified Fortifiable FILE No RELRO No canary found NX disabled No PIE No RPATH No RUNPATH 8) Symbols No 0 0 ./echo It looks like there&amp;rsquo;s not a whole lot of mitigations enabled in this binary. After firing up cutter and analyzing the binary we find that it&amp;rsquo;s not even linked against libc.</description></item><item><title>External</title><link>https://fernetinjection.github.io/posts/2021-02-01-external/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fernetinjection.github.io/posts/2021-02-01-external/</guid><description>Recon As usual, we&amp;rsquo;ll start off by taking a look at the mitigations enabled in the binary:
$ checksec --file=./external RELRO STACK CANARY NX PIE RPATH RUNPATH Symbols FORTIFY Fortified Fortifiable FILE Partial RELRO No canary found NX enabled No PIE No RPATH No RUNPATH 81) Symbols No 0 3 ./external Cool, there&amp;rsquo;s no PIE and no canary, that will simplify things a bit in case we find a buffer overflow.</description></item><item><title>Maze</title><link>https://fernetinjection.github.io/posts/2021-02-01-maze/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fernetinjection.github.io/posts/2021-02-01-maze/</guid><description>First impressions This challenge had the following description:
maze corparate just started a new trading platform, let's hope its secure because I got all my funds over there http://45.134.3.200:9000/ The URL provided us a web to hack with a simple login page:
The Login Form Our first attempt as hackers, is to always try common easy username-password combinations, but in this case they didn&amp;rsquo;t work. We decided to proxy the requests this site was doing to understand its behaviour, everything looked pretty clean.</description></item><item><title>The Pwn Inn</title><link>https://fernetinjection.github.io/posts/2021-02-01-the-pwn-inn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fernetinjection.github.io/posts/2021-02-01-the-pwn-inn/</guid><description>Recon First things first, let&amp;rsquo;s check what mitigations are enabled in the binary so that we can get a clear idea of what exploits are doable.
$ checksec --file=./the_pwn_inn RELRO STACK CANARY NX PIE RPATH RUNPATH Symbols FORTIFY Fortified Fortifiable FILE Partial RELRO Canary found NX enabled No PIE No RPATH No RUNPATH 82) Symbols No 0 2 ./the_pwn_inn I should add that the hint for this challenge includes: We've had many famous faces stay in our Inn, with gets() and printf() rating us 5 stars.</description></item></channel></rss>